Kaska Miskolczi

Atlanta Metropolitan Area



linkedin.com/in/batmanwgd



stddef@outlook.hu

Summary

Devising creative solutions to complex problems is my shtick. Critical thinking and inductive reasoning are the two primary reasons I chose a philosophically intensive bachelor's degree.

Concerning my career, fruition emerged through a balance of computational precision, aesthetic perspicacity, and a warm personality.

Professional interaction with a plethora of technologies over the years has been the crux of my experiences, but the concepts I'm most proficient encompass universal platform/architecture design, documentation, and development.

Szívélyes üdvözlettel

Experience



Sr. Consultant

Contractor

Dec 2014 - Present (5 years 6 months +)

Contracting in an effort to gain hyper-specialized acumen, while maintaining partnerships/collaborative projects with various government & private agencies, without having to forfeit my intelligent flight, automation and computer interaction intellectual property. Also seeking to finance and advanced cyber security degree.

For the Front-End:

Designing component libraries, translating static designs via PSDs into fluid and functional/interactive prototypes for web applications, mobile applications and animation projects. Also responsible for performing user research, user testing, storyboarding, character creations, journey workflows and software design documents.

For the Backend:

Performing maintenance tasks for C/C++ programs and operations involving the porting of legacy mainframe applications to C++ 14/17 and C99 standards within the cloud, via Azure, AWS, IBM Blue Matrix, GCloud, Firebase and Heroku. Working with kernels to create adaptable drivers, with the primary focus towards cyber security of associated systems, and cross-platform integrations on UNIX compatible hardware.

(Cloud and Cyber Consultant

RelayHealth

Jul 2018 - Nov 2018 (5 months)

Responsible for designing the infrastructure and the architecture planning for our mainframe eTAL systems to the Microsoft Azure and Amazon Web Services cloud platforms. Designed and later implemented principles of security, compliance and disaster recovery to ensure our guaranteed SLA of 99.999997%. Created customized virtual private clouds and consulted with our partners' software development teams, to effectively increase the security of our data, transport tunnels, and cloud virtual machines. Ultimately led these teams in the implementation of multi-factor authentication to satisfy all HIPAA and governmental compliance standards.



Senior User Interface Developer with Cyber Consulting

Booz Allen Hamilton

Oct 2017 - Jul 2018 (10 months)

Responsible for creation of user-facing data analysis reports, software applications, web and mobile applications, cloud SAAS solutions, etc. Also responsible for translating big-data into marketable reports and informational graphics/campaigns. Mastered D3js to create DOM manipulable/dynamic graphs and charting presentations for public users and government administrators alike. Finished out role with cyber security consulting for our firms' larger clients responsible for massive intelligence collection; specifically focused around the security of internet connections, and systems hardware integrity.

Fierce Marketing Software Developer with Marketing

FierceMarkets

Feb 2017 - Nov 2017 (10 months)

Responsible for assisting software teams with development tasks including but not limited to: learning platforms based in Drupal/Laravel LAMP and MEAN stacks, completing assigned support tickets directly interacting with clientele, and creating new automation enhancement tasks to improve our development and deployment processes. Affectionately referred too as the bug whispering, automation loving PHP unit tester.

Webmaster

Florida SouthWestern State College

Apr 2015 - Nov 2016 (1 year 8 months)

As the Webmaster for FSW, I played an integral role in providing expertise and college-wide consulting services in the analysis, development, and delivery of enterprise web applications and processes. I led a team of programmers, launched new creative and research targeted marketing campaigns, and designed an entirely custom website for Florida SouthWestern State College. The other 50% of my position was responsible for all digital marketing advertisements including digital signage for our campus-wide displays, and 3D animation for sporting events.



Associate Creative Director

B2B Studios, LLC

Jan 2013 - Oct 2016 (3 years 10 months)

Directly assisted the CEO in writing proposals and winning new client contracts for web and mobile application development projects. Managed a team of four designers and developers to led over thirty client projects built in LAMP and MEAN based web application technologies. Implemented a new Linux server system and firewall protocol, as well as a new project management software for the systems administrators to use with client hosting moving forward. Favorite part of the job included character drawing/sketches and 3D animation projects.

Senior Web Developer

Florida SouthWestern State College

Apr 2015 - Sep 2015 (6 months)

In the position as web developer for FSW, I was responsible for professional work supporting College-wide (all four campuses) web programming activity. Work included developing and maintaining internal and external Florida SouthWestern State College Web sites. I was also responsible for designing, developing, and automating web processes to support effective and efficient operations, while supporting the development and delivery of the College's Luminis web portal content.

Examples of essential functions include but are not limited too:

- * Develops complex programming applications, tests programs, implements web applications and system enhancements
- * Designs, analyzes, codes, documents, and implements applications that support, enhance and integrate with the College web presence.
- * Provides on-going support of enterprise and related web applications, as well as functional and technical problem resolution

Senior Consultant

Abbey Carpet and Floor

Dec 2013 - Jul 2014 (8 months)

Designed ASP/Classic.NET based sitecore applications, and extended them to include JS functionality for analytics tracking. Designed corporate SEO/SEM marketing initiatives for pay-per-click advertising campaigns and lead their implementation across both desktop and mobile platforms.

Script Writer

Florida Gulf Coast University

Dec 2009 - Mar 2013 (3 years 4 months)

Though positions with the university initially started as work-study or student-employee as a campus-wide script writer, helping theatre departments and the department of education write up their scripts for all interviews, speakers, etc. became a full time role as both an XSL-XML script writer and video encoding script automator. When leaving, was responsible for creation of all of our HD video content, including authoring the scripts, editing the video, encoding the media and then storing the media on cloud VMs allowing public accessibility internationally.

Aircraft Weight and Balanced Algorithmic Engineer UPS

Sep 2012 - Feb 2013 (6 months)

Responsible for maintaining programmatic calculations for weight and balances of cargo planes at the RSW hub. Also responsible for landing and lift off documentation/recovery, communications across airports and service centers, and implementing hazmat/FOD safety initiatives. Greatest accomplishment was creating a terminal program to automate our timing systems for flights.

Left position due to 3am start time.

Education

dequeUniversity

Professional Certification with IAAP, Certified Professional in Web Accessibility 2017 - 2018

Deque University offers a wealth of web accessibility information, packaged into online learning modules that you can access any time, anywhere, and at your own pace. You can walk through each module step by step, or you can use Deque University as a handy reference to find answers to specific questions related to your current projects, and learn everything you need to know to pass the IAAP certification exam (CPACC: Certified Professional in Accessibility Core Competencies) in Deque's IAAP certification exam preparation course.

Florida Gulf Coast University

Bachelor's Degree, Philosophy and AI 2009 - 2014

Neurolinguistics and Artificial Intelligence are the quazi-specialities I honed while in my course work for my BA. Though during my BA I lost my Apa and experienced significant personal difficulty, I am the first in my family to make it this far, and hope to pursue at least one Masters, and subsequently a PhD in similar studies.

Licenses & Certifications

- **Management** LinkedIn
- Symmetric Cryptography Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Learning Cryptography and Network Security LinkedIn
- **In Learning Apache Cordova** LinkedIn
- in Cassandra Data Modeling Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Introducing Maven LinkedIn
- in Validating and Processing Forms with JavaScript and PHP LinkedIn
- in Ethical Hacking: Session Hijacking LinkedIn
- in 3ds Max: Cinematography for Visualization LinkedIn
- in Building and Deploying a Full-Stack React Application LinkedIn
- **in** Python for Data Science Essential Training LinkedIn
- **in** Tableau 10: Mastering Calculations LinkedIn
- in Microsoft Dynamics CRM: Advanced Techniques LinkedIn
- **in** Applied Machine Learning: Algorithms LinkedIn
- in C++ Templates and the STL LinkedIn
- in Dynamics for Power Users: Reports, Charts, and Dashboards LinkedIn
- Advanced Microsoft Power BI LinkedIn
- **in** Financial Accounting Part 1 LinkedIn
- in Learning Kubernetes LinkedIn
- in React.js: Building an Interface LinkedIn
- in C++: Advanced Topics LinkedIn
- Code Clinic: R (2015) LinkedIn
- in DevOps Foundations: Infrastructure as Code LinkedIn
- in JavaScript: Security Essentials LinkedIn
- in C++ Design Patterns: Creational LinkedIn
- in Amazon Web Services: Networking LinkedIn
- in C++: Smart Pointers LinkedIn
- C++: Move Semantics LinkedIn
- Mindows Server 2016: Installation and Configuration LinkedIn
- in Test-Driven Development in C++ LinkedIn

- in Windows Server 2019: Configure Hyper-V LinkedIn
- in Vue.js Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Linux: Kernels and Logging for System Administration LinkedIn
- in Linux System Engineer: Network Bonding, IPv6, Routing, and Virtual Systems LinkedIn
- **in** Learning Ubuntu Desktop LinkedIn
- in Linux: System Information and Directory Structure Tools LinkedIn
- in Learning Ubuntu Server LinkedIn
- in Linux System Engineer: Networking and SSH LinkedIn
- **in** Database Clinic: MySQL LinkedIn
- **In Designing an Onboarding Experience with InVision and Sketch** LinkedIn
- Setting up a Red Hat Enterprise Linux Server LinkedIn
- in Learning NGINX LinkedIn
- in Learning Fedora Linux (2015) LinkedIn
- in Cocoa with Swift 3 Essential Training LinkedIn
- macOS Sierra for IT Administrators LinkedIn
- **in** Core Data for iOS and macOS Enterprise Developers LinkedIn
- **In Learning Java Applications (2016)** LinkedIn
- in Google Firebase for iOS: First Look LinkedIn
- in AutoCAD 2020 Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Learning iOS 10 App Development: 1 Create Your First App LinkedIn
- in Smarter Cities: Using Data to Drive Urban Innovation LinkedIn
- in Angular: Building an Interface LinkedIn
- AutoCAD Electrical Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Angular: Material Design LinkedIn
- in Learning Adobe Animate CC LinkedIn
- Artificial Intelligence Foundations: Machine Learning LinkedIn
- Artificial Intelligence Foundations: Machine Learning LinkedIn AfRM3SJqKojwNWj6KUYR3sub6gtB
- Machine Learning & Al: Advanced Decision Trees LinkedIn
- in Linux System Engineer: Advanced Disk Systems and System Backup LinkedIn
- in Creating Bots with the Microsoft Bot Framework, Part 1 LinkedIn
- in Creating Bots with the Microsoft Bot Framework, Part 2 LinkedIn
- in DevSecOps: Building a Secure Continuous Delivery Pipeline LinkedIn

- in Docker Essential Training: 1 Installation and Configuration LinkedIn
- in Giving Your Elevator Pitch LinkedIn
- in Learning AWS CloudFormation LinkedIn
- in Cloud Architecture: Advanced Concepts LinkedIn
- in Microsoft Cybersecurity Stack: Securing Enterprise Information LinkedIn
- in 3ds Max: Hard Surface Modeling LinkedIn
- in Azure Machine Learning Development: 3 Deploying and Managing Models LinkedIn
- Serverless Architecture LinkedIn
- Securing the IoT: Privacy LinkedIn
- in Implementing an Information Security Program LinkedIn
- in CCSP Cert Prep: 1 Cloud Concepts, Architecture, and Design LinkedIn
- **in** Designing an Animated App UI with Illustrator LinkedIn
- **In Drawing Vector Graphics: Isometric Illustration** LinkedIn
- in Machine Learning & Al Foundations: Linear Regression LinkedIn
- in Incident Response Planning LinkedIn
- in Learning Cloud Computing: Cloud Governance LinkedIn
- in Azure Administration: Manage Subscriptions and Resources LinkedIn
- in Mastering Puppet for Large Infrastructures LinkedIn
- CCSP Cert Prep: 2 Cloud Data Security LinkedIn
- in Amazon Web Services: Design and Implement Systems LinkedIn
- in Amazon Web Services: Implementing and Troubleshooting PaaS Products LinkedIn
- in Oracle Database 12c: Basic SQL LinkedIn
- **Mware NSX: Security** LinkedIn
- GDPR Compliance: Essential Training LinkedIn
- in SQL Server: Security for Developers LinkedIn
- Code Clinic: C++ LinkedIn
- in NoSQL Development with Azure Redis and C# LinkedIn
- in Ethical Hacking: Exploits LinkedIn
- in PowerShell: Scripting for Server Administration LinkedIn
- **Microsoft Office 365: Administration** LinkedIn
- in Windows Performance Toolkit: Detecting Memory Leaks LinkedIn
- in Electron: Building Cross Platform Desktop Apps LinkedIn
- in Learning COBOL LinkedIn

- R Programming in Data Science: High Volume Data LinkedIn
- in Introduction to Quantum Cryptography LinkedIn
- in Azure Security Technologies: Manage Identity and Access LinkedIn

Skills

C++ • JavaScript • Adobe Photoshop • Web Design • Research • User Experience (UX) • User Interface Design • Proposal Writing • 3D Visualization • Data Analysis